THE WONDERFOOLS
EPISODE 8
THE GUARDIANS OF HAESEONG CITY PART 2
Kim Pal-ho, our shepherd,
has been martyred.
Shepherd!
What do we do, Eun Chae-ni?
We're all doomed now.
I may be broke and pathetic,
but I'm still a father and a husband.
The head of my family.
My dear Cheong is only 14 years old.
Had I known an apocalypse was coming,
I would've bought her that CD player,
even if it meant being
up to my eyeballs in debt.
What are you crying for?
You could've just said that.
Would that change anything?
What could we even do?
They're Wunderkinder,
and apparently, we're just defective.
You're right.
Saying it wouldn't change anything.
So tie your shoelaces tight and get ready
to run.
What…
Stay back!
I'll slice you up!
She'll slice you up!
I'm Lady Trainwreck!
I'm Royal Nightmare!
Stay back!
Stop right there! Stay back!
Hey, Eun Chae-ni.
Take us somewhere else, anywhere!
I'd love to,
but I ate my last coffee jelly
to save Ro-bin.
I really hoped I'd get a chance
to say goodbye to Moon Mi-hui and Cheong.
Mr. Son.
Forget it. Don't comfort me!
Just my luck, I guess.
I worked my ass off
only to get treated like an ass.
The world's screwed up.
Was the financial crisis my fault?
Is it my fault my company restructured?
I'm a victim too.
Why am I always treated like a loser?
I don't ask for much!
Why am I always--
Finally, some peace and quiet.
It was a bit noisy, wasn't it?
He's not such a bad guy
once you get to know him.
He just likes to talk big.
SON GYEONG-HUN
MOON MI-HUI
Chae-ni, you little shit.
Alrighty, then.
Who's going to come at me first?
Hotteok lady?
Or Mr. Heo from the general store?
You're going to get hurt.
I wonder if you'll be all right with that.
One wrong move and you lose a finger.
Then who'd flip the hotteok?
Get her.
Hold up. Stay back!
Don't you dare touch me!
There are too damn many!
You'll get hurt!
Let go, damn it!
I told you not to. Why are you--
What do you want with me?
Outsiders!
Let's protect our temple!
Charge!
What the… What was that?
Everyone, freeze!
Get away from my granddaughter!
Grandma?
Eunie!
Grandma!
Take this.
Are you okay?
Look at you.
Did you crawl out of a dumpster?
Grandma, look at yourself first.
Did you not sleep at all last night?
Look at the bags under your eyes.
You'll collapse at this rate!
The owner of Hearty House?
What brings
you here?
There you are.
I thought you would have gone
to see your mom.
Why us?
I'm just curious why you did
those awful things to us.
There's no particular reason.
All of this started
with humanity's petty desire
to live a long life.
That's how the world works.
Things that may look grand on the outside
often come from
petty greed, petty envy,
and the most trivial of discoveries.
We needed children
to experiment on back then,
and you just happened to be one of them.
So,
don't seek reason or meaning.
There is none.
Life merely exists
upon banal coincidences and petty reasons
until we eventually perish.
Petty?
I guess human lives are trivial to you.
Out of the 72 children,
50% of them manifested,
and half of those who manifested
gained abilities.
One of them was the child
with the Heart of Eternity.
That child was the only
meaningful end product.
So I thought
if more people manifested,
then wouldn't the number
of eternal hearts also increase
at a similar probability?
Enough with the riddles.
Are you saying
you'll unleash that drug on Haeseong?
God sometimes brings destruction and chaos
to create a new order.
Are you
actually insane?
What about the children who died?
Among the children experimented on,
half died without ever manifesting.
And of those who manifested,
some died from the physical mutations.
Far more children died
than the few who survived.
For a single coincidence
that may or may not recur,
you're going to kill
all those people again?
It's not the dead children
who change history.
It's you, the survivors.
You actual son of a bitch.
Bring me the Child of Eternity again.
Let us create a new order
in a new world together.
Ko Eun-san.
You will become a new breed of humans.
On my way here, I wondered…
if I…
could kill you.
A pity.
I was quite fond of you.
Father.
Father!
Master.
Grandma.
Handle things here.
What about you?
I don't know if it'll work,
but I really need it to.
Please, let's go.
To Master.
Please!
Hot!
What the… Fire!
Master!
Master?
Oh dear, this isn't the right face.
It's not the right face.
This isn't the face I'm looking for.
I can't save you.
Master!
Help me.
Master's face doesn't look like this.
I'm sorry.
Damn it.
Chae-ni, my God--
Call 119!
Answer me! Damn, that's hot!
Master!
Eunie, that's enough.
We just called 119.
Grandma, he's not there.
Master.
I can't find him.
Father.
Father, it's me. Father?
Hey, Ju-ran.
We'll be in downtown Haeseong
in 15 minutes.
All right.
Don't let anything go wrong.
No matter what happens…
stick to the plan.
Ju-ran.
Everything's okay, right?
Yeah.
Everything's fine.
When's Pal-ho joining us?
Pal-ho can't make it, Ho-ran.
I'll send someone else instead.
Who?
I'm sorry about back then.
Sir!
Please open this door.
Sir, please!
Sir!
The debt I owe you from back then,
let me settle it now.
The door is wide open now,
so go and live your life to the fullest.
Okay?
Number 3972.
Can you hear me?
Yeah, okay. Bye.
Grandma.
One of the believers says
two container trucks headed downtown
early this morning.
What was loaded in them?
I don't know the details.
I just saw them leave early this morning.
They're loaded with a drug.
Royal Nightmare said he saw it.
They're planning to spray it
all over Haeseong.
Should we report it?
There's no point.
That bastard, Byeong-jin,
is already under the influence
of the Church.
I'd better meet the mayor first.
That won't be necessary.
Holy Mother.
Are you another one of those kids?
You look badly hurt.
Don't move.
Hey, Mr. Gu, are you insane?
What do you think you're doing?
Stop it.
Don't mess with Grandma or Mr. Gu.
If you have something to say,
say it to me. Don't mess with my family!
I already lost my brother
and my father.
Now it's your turn.
No!
She'll be back.
The moment she shows up,
shoot her.
If you want to live, move!
I said move!
Chae-ni, you're so freaking cool.
Here goes!
Here I go.
Yeah!
Eun Chae-ni, coming through!
Now! Get her out!
So refreshing.
Cheong.
What about Dad?
Don't worry about it, honey.
How dare he stay out all night.
At this point, he's asking for a divorce.
You're divorcing?
Don't worry about anything
and just focus on the rehearsal, okay?
Stand up straight!
Honey, say cheese!
Please just gather around for a moment.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you all so much.
I'm so grateful to see you
working so hard. Hello, Mayor.
Tonight's parade will start
exactly at eleven o'clock as planned.
As we rehearsed,
the order will be as follows.
First, the flag bearers,
then the marching band will follow.
Then, the Changwon Samulnori Troupe will--
Everybody, stop!
Everyone!
-Who, why? What is it?
-Everyone, stop!
Stop what you're doing, all of you,
and get out of here!
Everybody stop!
Stop what you're doing
and get out of here.
You can't stay here.
-Why not?
-You can't stay here!
What's going on, huh?
Honey! What are you doing over there?
Honey!
You're here too?
Cheong!
My darling Cheong as well?
You can't stay here.
Honey, come with me.
We have to go. This isn't a drill!
Why on earth are you doing this
in front of all these people?
That's how urgent and dangerous
the situation is. Let's go, now!
-Let's go!
-Go where?
Do you know how long
she's waited for today?
She was chosen to represent her grade,
not just her class.
What would you know?
Being the damn grade representative
doesn't matter right now!
The apocalypse is coming!
Seriously?
Screw the new millennium!
Everything will disappear in an instant!
If you keep embarrassing me like this,
you'll be the one to disappear.
From Cheong's life and mine.
Forever.
-Honey.
-Stop embarrassing me!
Honey, you have to listen to me!
-Come on.
-Mr. Yang.
Listen to me!
Please tell everyone to evacuate.
The guys at the Church
of Eternal Salvation.
Do you know what they're trying to do
to Haeseong?
I do.
You do?
They donated a whopping 100 million won
for this festival.
Thanks to them,
we were able to make a giant version
of our city mascot, Yang-soon,
and even have a fireworks show tonight.
It's all just a cover!
You mustn't fall for it!
Please just listen to me!
Damn it, that hurts!
First you said that a pigeon
blinked its eyes sideways like this,
then a carp this big winked at you.
That it was because of phenol
and dumped waste,
and now you're blaming it on the Church?
-That's right!
-Fine, okay.
For matters like these,
go ahead and file a complaint,
but please hold off for today.
It's a festival, after all.
The anticipated new millennium is upon us.
You can't rain on our parade like this.
Your daughter is even a flag bearer.
Cut it out.
Just call the police.
Royal Nightmare can't stand to see
other people happy.
-All right.
-Always grumbling.
-Come on now.
-He's always complaining.
I'll take care of it. I will.
Cheong.
Goodness, isn't he embarrassed
in front of his daughter?
-Exactly!
-That's a bit harsh.
His daughter is here listening, so…
Mr. Son?
Chae-ni!
Master is gone,
and Grandma isn't here either.
What do we do now?
What do you mean?
We'll face the apocalypse
like this, together.
Should we just run away by ourselves?
What a load of nonsense!
How could I leave Moon Mi-hui
and Cheong behind? Are you mad?
Chae-ni, what are we going to do?
Come to think of it,
I never got to take a picture with Master.
Excuse me?
How can you talk about pictures
at a time like this?
The apocalypse is coming for Haeseong!
You, me, everyone. We'll all be wiped out.
We're the only ones who know that,
but there's nothing
we can do about it. Why?
Because no one believes us. Why?
Because we're nobodies.
REWARD GRAPES
GREAT JOB
First, let's stop the trucks.
What trucks?
The trucks with the drug
are somewhere in Haeseong.
They're going to blow it up somewhere.
Where exactly?
Where else?
The place where the most people
are gathered in Haeseong right now.
Where do you think?
-Where?
-Sorry, excuse us.
-Move.
-Why's it so crowded?
-Please.
-Move.
-The mascot of Haeseong!
-Too crowded!
-Yang-soon.
Buy a Yang-soon T-shirt!
Look at Yang-soon!
Hey, isn't that Chae-ni?
Have you seen any
Church of Eternal Salvation trucks?
No, we haven't.
Leave Haeseong right now, okay?
Or you'll all die!
You'll die!
-Leave Haeseong.
-What did she say?
-Die?
-Leave!
What is she talking about?
This tastes awful.
What kind of truck is this? What kind?
Are you from the Church? What's in here?
-What is this woman doing?
-Guess not. Pass.
-Welcome.
-Okay!
Who are you?
What are you doing?
You're clueless!
What's he saying?
I did touch the goods,
but there's something really important--
Hey, shut it.
By the looks of you,
you're a repeat offender.
-Why I oughta…
-Don't judge me based on my looks--
Ro-bin!
You don't even have a clue!
What the heck, man!
You got your ass kicked already?
This is so exhausting.
Why are we even going to such lengths?
We have to save the people.
Why are we responsible for the lives
of people we don't even know?
True.
We don't have to save people
we don't know.
Right?
But we know everyone here.
Look.
We really do know everyone here.
Let's help the less fortunate.
So what do we do?
-Hello.
-Wishing you good health.
Yes, hello.
-Long time, no see.
-Yes, take care.
We don't even have friends,
so how do we know so many people?
Stop grumbling.
Let's hurry up and find them.
We don't have time!
Okay? Just go!
-They're here!
-I think they're here!
-The parade!
-You're right.
What is it?
-What is that?
-What?
Where are they?
Cheong.
ADIEU 1999, TOWARD THE YEAR 2000
A NEW MILLENNIUM, A NEW HOPE
MILLENNIUM GRAND FESTIVAL
HAESEONG 2000
One, two. One, two, three, four.
One, two, three.
-Chae-ni, wait up.
-Hurry!
I said wait.
-One second.
-Still so unfit.
Why? What is it?
Master?
You escaped?
When?
How?
I'm so glad you're safe.
I knew you would be, Master.
-Master.
-Master?
What'd you do that for?
I thought words were the only thing
that could hurt me.
I'm really upset right now, Master.
You know that?
There is nothing…
you can do.
There she is. There's my daughter.
Cheong!
My daughter's awesome.
So freaking fabulous.
Don't worry, Cheong.
I'll do whatever it takes to stop them.
-Stop what?
-You scared me! Honey.
Why don't you stop blocking the road?
We need to reserve a good spot
to see the fireworks.
-We can't go to see the fireworks.
-Move.
-Honey, please.
-I need to claim a good spot.
The fireworks.
Do you know what the Church
is trying to do to Haeseong?
I do.
They donated a whopping 100 million won
for this festival.
Thanks to them,
we were able to make a giant version
of our city mascot, Yang-soon,
and even have a fireworks show tonight.
That's it. The fireworks.
Up in the sky, in one go.
Boom!
Cheong!
Honey!
-Are you okay?
-Honey!
-Are you okay? Cheong!
-Where's Cheong?
Don't come here. Run!
Get behind me.
Are you okay?
Are you okay? Move!
Come this way.
Get inside. It's okay.
What the…
It's already started? I thought she was
sending someone else instead of Pal-ho.
Hey, Master.
Are you mad at us or something?
Let's talk it out.
It's her. The one with the gloomy face
who brainwashes and uses people.
She even made Mr. Gu
point a gun at Grandma earlier.
Really?
Chae-ni!
Master.
Master!
Chae-ni!
Chae-ni.
Snap out of it, Choi Un-jeong!
It's Lee Un-jeong.
I thought
you were really going to kill me.
How could you choke me so hard?
-Cars flying around…
-Stop talking and…
What the…
Why won't you listen?
What's with them?
Why are they acting like that?
Sir, where are you going?
Don't worry. I'm sure
our shepherd left some instructions.
-Really?
-He did?
Why? What's up there?
Where are you going?
No! You can't go there.
Where do you think you're going?
-Must be that way.
-They're strange.
-Should we go too?
-Shut it.
Something's up with them.
Chae-ni!
Master!
You two stay here.
No matter what happens, don't come out.
Am I clear?
Are you insane?
Where do you think you're going,
leaving us here?
You have to protect us!
I have to get out there to protect you.
What could you do out there?
What can you do about a car flying at you?
Think you can stop that
with your smart mouth?
Good point.
But it turns out there is something
I can do with my smart mouth.
If you go out there now,
I really will divorce you.
I'm serious this time.
No, honey!
I love you,
Mi-hui.
You dummy!
Mr. Son Gyeong-hun! What took you so long?
I'll handle the side with more people.
You take that side, Mr. Kang.
Can someone insult me?
Are you going to rely on
someone insulting you forever?
Why don't you try to drum up some strength
on your own, you oversized moron?
They're coming.
Isn't it fascinating?
I'm scared!
Get back!
Hey, stay back!
That wasn't me.
I'm your father!
I'm your mother!
I'm sorry.
No. Don't do it--
Ma'am?
Please insult me.
What?
Hurry.
For crying out loud.
How dare this rootless
good-for-nothing bastard
show up out of nowhere
and act like a bumbling idiot!
Should I pop your eyeballs out
and chew them up like radish kimchi?
Why, I should gouge your eyes out
and suck the ink out of them dry.
Want me to whoop your ass?
You dirty bastard with shit for brains.
Piss off, you rotten bastard!
Bam!
Honk honk!
Anyone who wants to roll around
with me, stick here!
This is so exciting!
This is so much fun!
Let's all go on a walk
Around the neighborhood
Wake up early in the dead of night
Walk around the neighborhood
Yang-soon says hello to us too
We all say hello
As we walk around the neighborhood
I swear, I've never…
You must be completely nuts.
You and your shenanigans!
We're back.
That
worked.
Yeah.
It worked.
-Ouch.
-Mr. Son!
Chae-ni! My goodness.
Cheong.
What did we
just see?
Superheroes?
Is it time to clean up now?
Are you even listening?
Did that really just happen?
Or is this a prank show?
I didn't hear anything about it.
That's why he was a special recruit.
For his superpower.
I thought he'd hit his peak.
To think he's even hotter than I thought.
Un-jeong--
I just hit them with this,
and the people over there…
Look!
Run!
-Just run!
-Should we go down here?
This really is endless.
She's brainwashing them.
This won't end unless we find her.
No, we have to stop the fireworks first.
There'll be fireworks at midnight,
and it's likely the drug is inside them.
They'll gather people on the streets
for the countdown
then, at midnight, with a single… boom!
Midnight is less than 30 minutes away.
So what do we do?
Deal with the brainwashing woman first,
or the fireworks?
I'll take care of the fireworks!
Mr. Kang, you go with her.
Mr. Son, you can find
the brainwashing woman.
She must be nearby.
Hurry!
I am Spider-Man.
I am a virgin ghost.
I am Frankenstein.
I'm the Hong Kong Granny Ghost.
Oh my!
Oh my goodness!
Hurry, Ms. Eun Chae-ni.
There it is.
-Chae-ni.
-We're in the right place.
Damn it.
Damn.
In these things here? Are these the drugs?
Where are the fireworks?
I'll check these.
Excuse me.
-What are you doing?
-Who are you?
Get out of there. It's dangerous.
One second.
What is it?
Something strange in the sky.
Goal!
That's enough!
Stop it.
I said stop it! People are getting hurt!
You may be in a cult,
but you're still meant to be a believer.
You can't openly use violence.
Can you hear me?
Listen to me first, you little shit!
Even if you're industry standard
and we're defective, this is wrong!
How dare you use your superpowers
in such a godawful way!
Can you hear--
Again! There you go,
interrupting me again!
How dare you keep interrupting
when an elder is talking to you!
Where did you learn such bad manners?
-Can you--
-I said stop!
Just stop it!
What did those people ever do to you
to deserve this?
Sure, let's say
Trainwreck and Sap deserve it.
What about me and Moon Mi-hui? And Cheong?
And all those other miscellaneous people.
What did they ever do to you
to deserve this? Why?
What's the reason?
People didn't care about
the pain we endured.
No interest at all.
So I don't care either,
whether or not they die.
Never been scolded by an elder, right?
Well, you picked the wrong person
to mess with today.
I'm going to finally drill some manners
into you today--
You little…
Ju-ran.
What happened?
Are you okay?
Ju-ran, are you okay?
Why did you push yourself like this?
You told us
not to use our powers recklessly.
Pal-ho is dead.
And so is Father.
Let's stop this now.
I don't want to lose you too, okay?
I can't forgive them.
I'll kill them all.
You still have me.
We have no one left, Ho-ran.
Avenge us.
All of them.
Destroy them all.
Please do that for me, Ho-ran.
Here they come.
Hey, are you okay?
No.
-My head hurts.
-Earlier, you were all…
They've snapped out of it.
Is it over or what?
Are you hurt badly?
I'm just a bit tired.
What happened with the fireworks?
You won't be able to stop it.
Ms. Eun Chae-ni?
It'll be so very pretty.
The truth is,
I've never seen fireworks
in person either.
My final goodbye.
All right,
there really isn't much left of 1999.
Are you all spending the last moments
of the 20th century with your loved ones?
There are about five minutes left
until the new millennium begins.
I'm hoping you're all spending
these last few minutes of 1999
with the people you cherish most.
This is the last song I'm playing for you
in the 20th century.
This is the price
of our shepherd Kim Pal-ho's blood.
Chae-ni!
Why, is something wrong?
Why? What is it?
Are you really Eun Chae-ni?
Of course I'm Eun Chae-ni.
Who else would I be, Geum Chae-ni?
What is it?
There…
There's another Chae-ni!
Why am I over there?
Did I just get stabbed?
No!
What's this?
Breathe. I need you to stay awake.
I'll call an ambulance.
Are you…
worrying about me?
Yeah.
-Look at that!
-Wow.
Just like you did
for me back then.
Wow, look at that fish!
You didn't just comfort me,
you comforted all the kids in there.
There are so many!
It…
would have been nice…
if you'd been on my side.
No.
Ho-ran.
No!
Is she dead? Is she really?
Her pulse is still there.
Can you call an ambulance?
Damn it, I think I dropped
my cell phone somewhere. Hold on.
Ro-bin, let's move her inside first.
Where could I have dropped…
Honey, where are you going?
Honey!
I told you not to come out
until I told you to.
Honey, where are you going?
What is that?
THE JUDGE IS STANDING AT THE DOOR
JAMES 5:9
You won't be able to stop it.
The prophecy will be fulfilled as planned.
You will know when the apocalypse comes.
Those who do not believe
will be cast into the hellfire
known as death.
As for those who are saved,
they will gain eternal life
as Wunderkinder!
So that was the real bomb.
It wasn't the fireworks?
Maybe it was never
something we could stop.
I said I wanted to live
to see the apocalypse.
I guess my wish came true.
But what a shame.
I no longer want to see
this goddamn apocalypse.
Chae-ni, what are you saying?
You're making me nervous.
Ro-bin, toss me and Mr. Son up there.
Why me?
There's nowhere to hold on to.
Just stick me on securely,
then you can fall off.
I'll try to teleport with that airship.
And what if something terrible
happens to you?
Don't worry.
You know that I don't die, even if I do.
Why would you not die? Don't you know
how that heart ended up with you?
If anything goes wrong, that heart
could be all that's left of you.
That's a bomb, you doofus.
If it explodes,
you'd be blown to smithereens.
What would we say to Grandma?
It'd be a secret, of course.
Don't tell her, Kang Ro-bin, okay?
I'll be back soon.
No.
Then let's go together.
I'll go up there with you.
In your state?
You'll just be a burden, okay?
Just make sure to catch us when we fall.
Catch Mr. Son first. Then me.
Ms. Eun Chae-ni!
You know I could die
if I fall from that height, don't you?
So I'm asking you to catch me.
It would be a darn shame
to die after completing the mission, no?
Hurry up. We don't have much time.
It'll be okay.
Okay.
Let's do it.
Why the hell not?
You look pretty today.
It's done.
You know what, Ro-bin?
You're fugly when you smile.
Eun Chae-ni, I swear, you…
Just toss us already, King Sap!
You Sappy Sap!
King Sap!
I
want Eun Chae-ni
to just
disappear
forever!
-Go!
-What?
You need to climb up.
Come on. Go a little further!
You go!
Wait, one second.
Just a bit more.
Don't fall off yet.
-Go!
-Stay stuck.
Go!
-Go!
-Wait a minute, Mr. Son.
Ow, easy!
I'm up.
Mr. Son, you should go now!
You were really impressive today.
Hey.
Do good, you punk!
Still,
I hope Eun Chae-ni comes back
safe and sound!
All right,
we really don't have much time left now.
Let's start the countdown.
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six,
five,
four,
three,
two,
one!
Eunie.
The year 2000!
The new millennium has finally begun.
No.
No!
Where am I?
-What is that?
-In the sky!
What happened?
I should be watching this with Cheong.
What a view!
We stopped it.
We
saved these people.
When Chae-ni comes back,
please make sure you catch her, Master.
Yeah.
She's late. Did she go somewhere far?
Did she go to Canada again?
Even if she went to the North Pole,
not Canada,
she should've been back by now
because she'd be teleporting.
Damn it.
Stop saying dumb stuff.
And so, the year 2000 began
with nothing out of the ordinary.
Finally, the new millennium has begun.
With the start of the year 2000,
we have some news of an incident.
Last night,
a sudden squall occurred in Haeseong.
During its Millennium Festival…
My goodness,
what kind of squall flips over cars?
And it ruined the parade too.
Still, Cheong looks great
in these pictures.
Do you really not remember?
Do you really not remember how cool I was
when I saved you two that day?
I took you to shelter in the record store.
And then I saved people and stuff,
you know?
Now you're resorting to telling
outlandish lies?
Why not just say you flew around
with a cape on?
I'm so sick of you.
-Dad.
-Yeah?
-My lunch box.
-Didn't I give it to you?
There it is.
They are absolutely ridiculous.
Unbelievable…
And no one remembered the events
that took place that day.
A squall?
How could a squall blow a car away?
Tell me about it.
How did you get this?
What the…
Why doesn't anyone remember?
Could it be…
Honey.
Honey!
Why are you standing there?
Honey, yes, it's me.
I saved you and Cheong,
and I saved everyone.
What are you on about?
I don't see Cheong. Go and find her.
Cheong!
Son Cheong!
No, I saved you…
We did it!
We saved you and Haeseong
from the apocalypse!
So why don't you remember?
For some unknown reason,
the heroes of that day
disappeared from everyone's memories.
Why?
Why do you all look so clueless?
For God's sake! Do you really think
this car flipped over from a squall?
But
I…
My darling daughter.
Have a good day today too, okay?
You did great, Dad.
Yeah.
What?
Yeah, thanks, Cheong.
Thank you, honey.
HEARTY HOUSE
She'll come back.
My baby will come back, yes.
She just went too far,
so she's taking a while
to find her way back.
Well…
that's possible, isn't it?
Yeah.
FLORALA
Those little shits.
They say you have to make a grave,
even if it's empty,
for someone who died away from home.
So that their soul doesn't wander
the netherworld aimlessly.
MEMORIAL TABLET
EUN CHAE-NI
Enjoy.
Please enjoy.
Not much to eat here.
What kind of party is this?
You shouldn't eat with your hands.
Then hurry up with the serving.
Sorry, we're just giving out
generous portions.
If you're starved, come here.
I'll serve you first.
Is this for a 49-day ritual?
Did someone die?
Who died?
You…
Eunie.
Is that you, Eunie?
Chae-ni!
You mean Eun Chae-ni?
Goodness!
Goodness gracious!
Good heavens!
My goodness, Chae-ni.
Let me look at you. My goodness.
It took me a while to get back, didn't it?
I tried to go
to the furthest place I knew,
and I ended up in a desert
on the other side of the planet.
And I guess it was too far away
because I couldn't make my way back.
I had no passport, no money.
So the journey back here
was absolutely grueling.
But who died? Everyone's here.
-My baby isn't dead.
-Who?
My baby isn't dead, is she?
My baby's alive!
Wait.
Wait, I'm starving, okay?
Give me some food first.
-Food.
-Right, food.
You brat!
How can you be so unfazed?
Do you know how sad we were?
I knew better than anyone
that I wasn't dead,
so why would I be sad?
Is that so?
I guess you're right!
Can we get a wet towel here?
You stinky little shit.
I do stink, don't I? Have you been good?
Food.
Oh, my baby.
The rice cakes are good today.
Aren't you happy to see me, Master?
What took you so long?
It took me a while
to get used to being a stowaway.
Why? Did you miss me?
It was a refreshing change,
not having someone cling to me.
Stay back, you.
You try not washing for three weeks.
I bet you'd smell worse!
Let's meet again after you've washed up.
You won't be able to wash this off
with a shower.
It'll last a whole week.
You're…
such a pain, Ms. Eun Chae-ni.
I like you.
Some people are different.
Others are late bloomers.
Others
prefer the quiet outskirts.
HAESEONG CITY HALL
But
there's no such thing
as a nobody.
-Yes?
-Is it done yet?
No, just a moment.
Just bring me what you have so far.
Okay.
Oh, for crying out loud.
I told you to go back to Seoul!
I don't know why you're still here,
driving me nuts.
Next time, I'll do it all.
Here, get this done quickly.
CHURCH OF ETERNAL SALVATION
Yes, the entrance has been blocked off.
-Anything left?
-It's all charred.
Search every inch.
And report to me if you find anything.
Yes, sir.
Subtitle translation by: Jimin Choi